Have you ever looked at a car and thought,
When I ask people that, they tell me
And I keep thinking, is that still it?
No improvements for a hundred years?
Things need to change.
The original idea for the net was for computers to share computing power,
And today its main purpose is to look at fat cats.
I genuinely believe that if we do not improve the car,
we will stop using them within two years.
And that's where I come in.
Hello, Kickstarter.
Let me introduce you to my first car brand:
Imagine a car as a multimedia, multiroom, 24/7 interconnected platform,
where you can chill with your bros and broettes.
Now, if you're anything like my bank loan officer, you will say
"Mr Kilian,"
And I calmly explained to him:
IT'S NOT AN RV YOU IGNORANT WHORESON.
NOT THAT A THICKHEADED PIECE OF HUMAN FECAL MATTER WOULD EVER UNDERSTAND.
Though people that live in RVs used to be my most loyal customers in a previous venture I can't talk about.
Now I want to create a car that is innovative and not suspicious looking,
that revolutionizes what a car 2 car can 2 be.
For example, as a working mother, I hate when I drive my kids and they always have to use the bathroom.
And that's why every Kilrrari comes equipped with an organic toilet.
And an air filtration system that will remove bad smell, and all other potential deadly toxins.
You see, safety is our number one concern.
That's why there are no passenger windows.
In 100% of car accidents, the cars had windows.
Yet the biggest reasons for collisions are those darn distractions.
Teenagers and their phones, amirite?
That's why every Kilrrari comes with a signal jammer that makes it impossible to check social media,
contact friends or contact the police or whatever.
Now, if you're anything like my business advisor, you might say,
"Um, M-Mr Kilian,"
And I calmly explained to her:
IT'S NOT AN RV YOU BRAINDEAD TIGER PENIS.
GOD I FUCKING HATE YOU.
I know, I know, none of these features will change the world, but let me tell you what will:
Everyone is saying electric cars are the future.
I disagree.
My phone is electric, and it's annoying to recharge all the time.
I wish I could just buy some gasoline and fill it up.
We at Kilrrari have developed a crystal-based fuel,
that can be made in every car,
using toxic and explosive material.
Every Kilrarri comes with instruments and a nice oak table.
People will buy the car, drive to the middle of nowhere and make batches of these crystals.
That just happen to be extremely addicting and cause your teeth to fall off.
Now, if you're anything like my local police officer, you might say,
"Mr Kilian,"
And I calmly explained to him,
IT'S NOT AN RV--
I want to see a lawyer.
This is the future.
Sadly, like every great innovator, I've run into a small legal dispute.
So your kickstarter money will cover certain legal costs.
And if we don't raise the money by saturday, I will be taking a short vacation.
For nine years.